[
  {
    "question": "What is Chance the Rapper's real name?",
    "answer": "Chancelor Jonathan Bennett",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Kendrick Lamar",
      "Shawn Carter",
      "Donald Glover"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city was Chance the Rapper born?",
    "answer": "Chicago",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Houston",
      "Los Angeles",
      "New York"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Chance the Rapper's debut mixtape called?",
    "answer": "10 Day",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Acid Rap",
      "Coloring Book",
      "The Big Day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous rapper collaborated with Chance on the song 'No Problem'?",
    "answer": "Lil Wayne",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Travis Scott",
      "Kanye West",
      "Drake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "For which song did Chance the Rapper win the Grammy Award for Best Rap Performance?",
    "answer": "No Problem",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Blessings",
      "All We Got",
      "Same Drugs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which president's daughter did Chance the Rapper campaign for during the 2020 election?",
    "answer": "Joe Biden",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Donald Trump",
      "Barack Obama",
      "Hillary Clinton"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the title of Chance the Rapper's debut studio album?",
    "answer": "The Big Day",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Coloring Book",
      "Acid Rap",
      "10 Day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which television show did Chance the Rapper host in 2019?",
    "answer": "Saturday Night Live",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon",
      "The Ellen DeGeneres Show",
      "Late Night with Seth Meyers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Chance the Rapper married to?",
    "answer": "Kirsten Corley",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Rihanna",
      "Beyonc√©",
      "Cardi B"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which film did Chance the Rapper make a cameo appearance in as a werewolf?",
    "answer": "Slice",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "La La Land",
      "Get Out",
      "Moonlight"
    ]
  }
]